To Whom It May Concern.

My Name is Anthony J. Manenti -

I am a Graduate of UNC Greensboro's College of Arts and Sciences and a recent graduate

of UNC's Coding Bootcamp.

In Bootcamp I was exposed to HTML, CSS, Javascript, MySQL, MongoDB, React and

Node. These tools have given me relevant hands on experience in industry leading

technologies. I have used this hands on experience to develop my proficiency in other

languages as well. I enjoy the creative work involved in making truly unique and

compelling applications and user interfaces.

I enjoyed the experience of working with other classmates to create and present two

full stack applications. During this time I learned the importance of self analysis and

learning to be comfortable with technologies and techniques that would challenge me.

I also learned the importance of communicating and sharing ideas.

I have over a decade worth of work experience in Information Technology. I started from

humble beginnings as a computer repair technician and have worked with managed

service providers in the triangle area. My work has always pushed me, and has been

humbling. I feel that there is always something new to learn.

I believe that I have the potential to be a valuable asset to any creative team. I have a

continued interest in the field and work constantly, even outside of the Bootcamp to

develop my skills and widen my breadth of experience.

Yours truly,

Anthony J. Manenti
Applicant

https://github.com/imaginethat01

ANTHONY J. MANENTI

Professional Resume:

Education:

• The Coding Bootcamp at The University of North Carolina

Intensive course in Full Stack Development

Fluency in MERN Stack and the development of dynamic applications using front and back-end technologies and database query languages. Project Management experience including two full stack applications.

• University of North Carolina - Greensboro

Bachelors of Arts and Sciences

Concentration: English Literature. Publishing. Design.

Work History:

• Imagine That Solutions

2013 - 2018 Primary Account Representive

Responsible for the creation and maintenance of eCommerce solutions and the management of analytics powered advertising tools

• The Computer Cellar Durham

2017-2018 Repair Technician

Polished the craft of laptop and small device repair. Successfully navigated difficult problems relating to common consumer hardware ans software.

• The ITGuys

2017-2018 Technical Specialist

Responsible as an MSP to a list of clients. And assistant in the installation of business and enterprise class networking assets.

• Intrex Computers INC / Microbarn.com

2013-2015 Lab Technician, Warehousing Agent.

Learned the fundamentals of diagnostics and computer repair, accounting and how to manage large sets of inventory.

PERSONAL REFERENCES



List of Relevant Contacts:

Current Employer (Computer Cellar Durham)

Daryn O'Shea (Owner) 919-824-3035

Gabriel Caviness (Supervisor) 919-949-1392

Simon Beery (Co-Worker) 919-370-6929

Educational Training (Coding Bootcamp UNC- Chapel Hill)

Will Pike (Instructor) 949-527-0499 pike.wil@gmail.com

Maria Wong (Teachers Assistant) mwong770@gmail.com

Ariel Borochov (Teachers Assistant) ariel.borochov@aol.com

Tim Tucker (Classmate) 615-956-5179

Personal Mentor (RedHat Support)

William Clarke 919-597-1046